uwex.edu 2014-12-02

# Privacy Policy - UW-Extension

## Privacy Policy 

#### I. Introduction

This statement discloses the privacy practices for UW-Extension's website www.uwex.edu. Protecting the privacy of website visitors is important to UW-Extension. We want to ensure that users understand what information we collect and how it is used. 

#### II. Voluntarily Information

We will not collect personally identifiable information from you other than what you supply to us voluntarily. For example, when you fill out the "Contact Us" form on this site, you will be asked for your email address. This information helps us reply to your request as well as tailor the site to your interests. This information is also used in aggregate form for statistical purposes.

UW-Extension will not share your personal information with third parties except as may be required by law.

#### III. Network and Web Server Logs

When you visit www.uwex.edu, UW-Extension's Web servers automatically collect and store limited information about your computer's connection to the Internet. 

The information collected allows us to make our site more useful to visitors. We do record some or all of the following information: 

  * The Internet Protocol address (IP address) of the machine you used to access our Web site. Your IP address is a number that lets computers attached to the Internet know where to send you data. Your IP address does not identify you personally. 
  * The date and time you visited www.uwex.edu
  * The pages visited on www.uwex.edu
  * The Web browser, type of computer and operating system used to access our site
  * A list of files downloaded or viewed
  * The amount of time spent viewing files

These data DO NOT contain any personally identifiable information. Data are used to analyze website traffic and make improvements to www.uwex.edu.

UW-Extension Web servers have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.

#### IV. Website Metrics

The UW-Extension uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. ("Google"). Google Analytics uses "cookies," which are text files placed on your computer, to help determine how visitors use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Google will use this information to evaluate your use of the website, compile reports on website activity for website operators and provide other services relating to website activity and Internet usage. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google's behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google.

You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser; however, please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website. By using this website, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes described above. 

#### V. Applicable Law

The UW-Extension complies with the Federal Trade Commission 1998 Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) ([www.ftc.gov/ogc/coppa1.htm](http://www.ftc.gov/ogc/coppa1.htm)) and Wisconsin Open Records Law. The laws of the state of Wisconsin govern the UW-Extension Privacy Policy.

#### VI. Acceptance of the uwex.edu Privacy Policy

By using this website, you agree to the terms and conditions of the UW-Extension Privacy Policy. Please check this page periodically for changes to our policy. Your continued use of www.uwex.edu following any changes indicates acceptance of those changes. If you have any questions or concerns, please contact us.

We assume responsibility only for www.uwex.edu. Be aware that sites we link to are not under UW-Extension's control. Privacy protections of those linked sites may differ. 

Effective Date: July 12, 2010
